{
    "id": "544791a1298d40a28dac8fb3d5b171b3",
    "title": "Editing Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Few of people can say that they always tell the truth.",
            "description": "We use few without of before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "that",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I always take an umbrella if in case it rains.",
            "description": "In case is similar to if but they are not interchangeable. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "in case",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The first time I have met him was last year.",
            "description": "We cannot use the present perfect with past time expressions.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "met",
                "last"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "As you know that next Friday's meeting has been called.",
            "description": "We use as or that. We cannot use them both.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "has",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We went out despite of the rain.",
            "description": "Despite is used without of.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "of",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a garage opposite of my house.",
            "description": "Opposite is used without of.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "opposite",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Although she had prepared well for the test, but she could not pass.",
            "description": "Although and but are both used to connect contrasting ideas. Use only one of them in a sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "but",
                "Either but or although"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "As he was not there so I left a message with his mother.",
            "description": "As indicates the reason and so indicates the result. Use only one of them in a sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "Either as or so"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is Jane who she works with me.",
            "description": "The relative pronoun who acts as the subject of the relative clause. Since a clause needs only one subject, we cannot write she.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "she",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They have got married a couple of months ago.",
            "description": "We cannot use the present perfect tense with past time expressions.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "a",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the guy whom we have met yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "have",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Because I have great respect for him so I listened to him.",
            "description": "Because shows the reason and so shows the result. Use only one of them in a sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "have",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}